Come, let's have a drink.
Come.
Cheers!
You were all invited by Young Master Li.
Have a seat, Groom.
It hasn't been this lively here in a long time.
You must be starving.
Here.
Eat something first to line your stomach.
Drink up!
Here.
Have another glass.
Jiushuang.
Do you know how much effort it took to find this place?
Just to save you.
Jiushuang, let's go.
Jiushuang.
Why aren't you saying anything?
A ghost!
It's a ghost!
Chun'er!
The bride has arrived!
Mother!
Tiankun.
Let's go.
The Honored Parents have arrived!
Continue.
Come on, fill 'em up!
Distinguished guests,
I declare the wedding officially begun!
The wedding officially begins!
First bow to Heaven and Earth!
Tastes pretty good.
Here, try this, it's good.
Come on, cheers!
Tell them to keep it down.
The guests Young Master Li invited...
why are they so rude?
Master,
Young Master Li didn't invite anyone.
Then who sent them?
Here.
Cheers!
Drink some more.
Who are you people?
How dare you crash the Qi Family's wedding!
Master,
It must just be an illusion.
As a Feng Shui Family,
we're not afraid of this.
Let the ceremony continue.
Quick!
Second bow to the parents!
Why did my father turn into a zombie?
Young Master Li, what's wrong?
Qi Tiankun.
There's something weird about this secret room.
Grab the Talisman Book and leave quickly.
The Talisman Book should be in the coffin.
Mother!
Where's my mother?
Is the Talisman Book in the coffin?
Go, quickly!
Go on!
Go!
Save me!
Save me, Tiankun!
Mother!
Save me!
Tiankun!
Quick, help me!
Mother!
I'll strangle you!
Qi Tiankun, I'll strangle you!
Give me back my leg!
I'll strangle you!
I'll kill you!
Qi Tiankun!
Go!
Go on, keep acting.
Li Xiao!
You're looking for this, right?
The Qi Family's Talisman Book.
So you have it.
Give me the Talisman Book.
Chun'er!
How did you let this kid fool you?
Come here, quickly.
Chun'er.
I am truly devoted to you and the Wan family.
This foolish Mei woman means nothing to me.
As long as we're together,
I can gather the Talisman, Curse, Seal, and Eye.
When that happens,
I can lead everyone
to break the curse on your four clans.
How touching.
Zhang Tianyou.
I know you have the Hard Armor on you.
But they don't, do they?
Bring me the Talisman Book right now!
Otherwise,
don't blame me if I kill them all.
Li Xiao,
do you really think that with all these things,
you can find the Tidal Tomb from twenty years ago?
You'll never find it without the Dragon-Seeking Formula!
What the hell do you know?
I found out a long time ago.
The Zhang family didn't all die off twenty years ago.
There's still a descendant left.
Did you find him?
Once I become Head of the Four Clans,
I'll find him soon enough.
Once I use the Dragon-Seeking Formula to find that tomb,
all the golden treasures inside will be mine.
As for whether I'll seal that thing up while I'm at it,
that depends on how Wan-Mei-Qi-Sheng begs on their knees.
There are no treasures there!
It's a lie!
Don't test my patience!
Give me the Talisman Book!
Or I'll kill them right now.
Hurry!
Qi Tianting, you bastard!
You killed my Mother!
I'll make you wish you were dead!
Cousin!
Sit here and don't move.
Watch how I deal with that piece of trash.
Hurry!
Brother Tianyou!
Should've done this from the start.
Qi Tiankun!
Qi Tiankun, you bastard!
Get the hell out here!
Qi Tiankun!
Get the hell out!
You want to kill me?
You killed my Mother.
I won't let you die so easily.
Brother.
You're even more useless than that Sheng family trash now.
I'm going to make you watch
how I toy with your women.
Bastard!
Take this!
Zhang Tianyou!
After I kill you,
I'll gouge out your eyes
and make you watch
how I take care of these three women for you.
Li Xiao,
take a good look at what's in your hand.
Don't move!
How is this possible?
What kind of illusion did you use?
That skeleton I saw earlier...
You set that up too, right?
Just figured it out?
I won't bother explaining
how the magnetic field and corpse miasma here
messed with your senses,
because your life isn't in my hands right now.
Sister Mei,
he lied to you before
and tried to kill you.
You should kill him.
Kill him?
I'm afraid of dirtying my hands.
I don't mind getting my hands dirty.
I'll kill him.
I'm fine.
Young Master.
We're here.
Perfect timing.
Zhang Tianyou!
Now even heaven is on my side.
How can you possibly fight me?